<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tip / Guides / Notes on PinGod AddOns</title><link>https://FlippingFlips.github.io/pingod-addons-docs/todo/tips-guides/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Tip / Guides / Notes on PinGod AddOns</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://FlippingFlips.github.io/pingod-addons-docs/todo/tips-guides/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blank Empty Projects</title><link>https://FlippingFlips.github.io/pingod-addons-docs/todo/tips-guides/new-project/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FlippingFlips.github.io/pingod-addons-docs/todo/tips-guides/new-project/index.html</guid><description>In the examples directory is a folder named !template. This is bare bones minimum. If on windows just copy and paste this folder in the examples and rename it to your name.
What&amp;rsquo;s in the folder? Properties This contains a launchSettings.json for launching the project inside Visual Studio. These are launch profiles and you can add your own in this file.
_link_addons.bat This file is explained in previous here but it will link the addons folder into the game so you are not duplicating files, just reusing the addons.</description></item><item><title>PinGodGame Projects - New From Template</title><link>https://FlippingFlips.github.io/pingod-addons-docs/todo/tips-guides/create-pingodgame-template/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FlippingFlips.github.io/pingod-addons-docs/todo/tips-guides/create-pingodgame-template/index.html</guid><description>Duplicate Template Copy the pingod-projects-template and paste in same directory, by default windows adds - Copy to the directory Rename the copy to pingod-projects-myproject You will need to link the addons again. Delete addons directory then run the _link_addons.bat project.godot file You can add a project name to the project.godot file before running the project. These are found under [application] in the config section. Yours will be empty.
The reason why we&amp;rsquo;ve added Projects-MyProject here is that it&amp;rsquo;s easier to tell the type in the appdata, because this is the name it will be saved under in the users app data.</description></item><item><title>PinGodGame Projects - Add a C# Script</title><link>https://FlippingFlips.github.io/pingod-addons-docs/todo/tips-guides/create-pingodgame-template-script/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 15:26:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://FlippingFlips.github.io/pingod-addons-docs/todo/tips-guides/create-pingodgame-template-script/index.html</guid><description>Create Script for MyScene This template project will not give any errors if you don&amp;rsquo;t use a C# script but if using an existing scene that uses a script then we will need to add a C# project to the directory.
As we&amp;rsquo;ve referenced a C# script from the SwitchOverlay.tscn then we need to make a C# project.
Fortunately that is easy as we just have to make a new script to do this.</description></item></channel></rss>